Finding Aid for the Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) collection, 1964-1994
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ephemera., 1977-1982, n.d..; Series 11.; Boxes 6, 8, and 19
  - WAVPM stickers., [n.d.].; 1 roll (Box 19)
    orange with black, color-imprinted lettering that reads "Pornography is a Lie About Women" and spells out full name for WAVPM: Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media.
- Publicity and Publications, n.d.., 1969-1981.; Series 12.; Boxes 1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 8, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26 and 27
  Clippings and reprints of articles related to Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW), WAVAW-authored articles, articles about WAVAW, books, annual reports, directories, federal, state and local government publications, newspapers, newsletters, periodicals and work diaries. Includes full run of the national newsletters produced by the Los Angeles chapter of WAVAW.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title or publication title, and then chronologically by date.
  - Newspapers., 1975-1994.; Oversized boxes 16-18
    Arranged alphabetically by publication title, and then chronologically by date.
    - Los Angeles Times., 1983-1985.
      Extensive collection of full-sized issues of the Los Angeles Times was removed from the collection. Keyword search terms for these discarded issues include: abortion, abortion clinic, anti-pornography ordinance, at-home mother, child-care advocacy, child-care subsidy, child killer, child molestation, civil rights, crime, discrimination, ERA, Hugh Hefner, Hustler magazine, Jerry Falwel, kidnapping, Larry Flynt, mental health, murder, National Council of Jewish Women, NCJW, Playboy, pornography, radical feminism, rape, rapist, Reagan Administration, robbery, Roe vs. Wade, sadomasochism, sex films, sex offender, sex slave, sexual abuse, sexual assault, sexual harassment, Snuff film, teen pregnancy, violence and voyeur dining.
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Clippings., 1979 -1991.; 3 folders (Box 1, Folders 24 - 26)
      Topics include: antipornography ordinance, discrimination against children, heterosexuality, anarchism, and rape.
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Fact sheets and brochures., 1981-1983, n.d..; 2 folders (Box 1, Folders 29 - 30)
      Topics include: sexism, women's education, racism, deafness, disability, sex bias in schools, children's anger, children with learning disabilities and parenting.
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - I Wish the Hitting Would Stop a Workbook for Children Living in Violent Homes., 1987-1990.; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Includes 1987 version and 1990 revision which includes Facilitator's Guide
  - Directories., 1974-1990.; Boxes 1, 4, 13 and 25
    - Record World Annual Directory and Awards Issue., 1979, July.; 1 issue (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Work diaries., 1977, 1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 13 and 14
    - Work diary for Dani Adams., 1985.; 2 folders (Box 1, Folders 31 - 32)
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Clippings., 1977, 1983.; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Topics include: violence against women, child abuse and learning disabilities
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Feminization of Poverty., 1983, May.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Los Angeles Feminization of Poverty Hearing
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Clippings., 1971-1986.; 2 folders (Box 4, Folders 19 - 20)
      Topics include: First Amendment, maternity leave, abortion, radical-feminist movement, feminism and sexuality, women in the military, prostitution, rape, sexual stereotypes and single mothers.
  - Directories., 1974-1990.; Boxes 1, 4, 13 and 25
    - L.A. (Area) Women's Yellow Pages., 1979.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 21)
      2nd Edition
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Neworld., 1978.; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Article entitled "Images of Women in Rock."
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Clippings., 1972-1982.; 2 folders (Box 7, Folders 14 - 15)
      Some article reprints included.
    - Articles about WAVAW., 1972-1982.; 2 folders (Box 8, Folders 9 - 10)
    - Industry Press., 1976-1978, [n.d.].; 2 folders (Box 8, Folders 11 - 12)
    - Movement Press., 1976-1979.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Straight Press., 1976-1978.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - WAVAW-authored., 1977-1978.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Victimology 1978 article and Cultural Sanction for Violence by Julia London.
  - Newsletters., 1974-1993.; Boxes 8, 10, 14 and 21
    Complete run of Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) newsletters produced by the Los Angeles chapter, partial run of Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media (WAVPM) newsletters, partial run of Feminist Alliance Against Rape newsletters and other newsletters produced by various women's and feminist organizations and women's crisis centers.
    - Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) chapter newsletters., 1980-1981.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Newsletters of the Minneapolis chapter of WAVAW.
    - Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) newsletters., 1977, May - 1983, Feb.; 3 folders (Box 8, Folders 17 - 19)
      Full run of the national newsletters produced by the Los Angeles chapter of WAVAW.
    - Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media (WAVPM) newsletters., 1977-1983.; 3 folders (Box 8, Folders 20 - 22)
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Report., 1979, July.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
      "The Politics of Rights: Civil Liberties in the 95th Congress."
    - California Mental Health Plan., 1980-1983.; 2 folders (Box 10, Folders 18 - 19)
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Clippings., 1977-1980.; 5 folders (Box 10, Folders 20 - 24)
      Topics include: pornography, rape, domestic violence, violence against women, First Amendment, and courts and corporations.
      Some articles about WAVAW included.
  - Newsletters., 1974-1993.; Boxes 8, 10, 14 and 21
    - Feminist Alliance Against Rape newsletters., 1974-1978.; 2 folders (Box 10, Folders 26 - 27)
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Legal pamphlets., 1970-1978.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Topics include: child abuse, The Television Code, women's rights and class power in Los Angeles.
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - New West The Magazine of California., 1981, Jan.; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Newsletters., 1974-1993.; Boxes 8, 10, 14 and 21
    - Newsletters (other than WAVAW)., 1976-1981, [n.d.].; 5 folders (Box 10, Folders 30 - 34)
      Topics include: rape, domestic violence, violence against women, martial arts/self defense and reproductive rights.
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - Publicity for new book releases., 1978.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Chrysalis, a quarterly magazine of women's culture., 1977, 1979.; 2 issues (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Civil Liberties Review., 1978, Jan/Feb.; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Article on censorship and the women's movement.
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - Comic book., 1987, July.; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
      El Libro Policiaco de Color New York Central Park Police Station
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Connexions, An International Women's Quarterly., 1981, May.; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Eros., 1981, Dec.; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Journal of Communication., 1981, Spring.; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Cult Film Audience
    - Ms.., 1976, Nov; 1982, June/Aug; 1983, Jan.; 4 issues (Box 11, Folders 7 - 8)
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Programs., 1981-1983.; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
      The Last ERA Walk Women's Equality Day and The First Decade Celebrating the Tenth Anniversary of the Woman's Building
    - Report of the Task Force on Women in Public Broadcasting., 1975, Oct.; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Published by the Corporation for Public Broadcasting
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Savvy., 1984, Sept.; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - The Not-So-Helpless Female., 1973.; 1 book (Box 11, Folder 12)
      by Tish Sommers
  - Publicity binders., 1969-1981.; Boxes 12 and 13
    Newspaper clippings relating to WAVAW and WAVAW-related issues formerly housed in binders.
    - Child abuse., 1969, 1979-1980.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Domestic violence against women., 1977, Jan - 1980, Aug.; 2 folders (Box 12, Folders 2 - 3)
    - Incest., 1979-1980.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Rape., 1976, Nov - 1980, Aug.; 7 folders (Box 12, Folders 5 - 11)
    - Rape, domestic violence and violence against women., 1990, Sept - 1981, Apr.; 5 folders (Box 12, Folders 12 - 16)
    - Sexual harrassment., 1978, Aug - 1980, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Directories., 1974-1990.; Boxes 1, 4, 13 and 25
    - Annotated Index/Directory of Women's Media., 1977-1981.; 2 folders (Box 13, Folders 1 - 2)
  - Publicity binders., 1969-1981.; Boxes 12 and 13
    - Entertainment industry., 1976, Nov - 1980, Aug.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Directories., 1974-1990.; Boxes 1, 4, 13 and 25
    - Guide to Women's Resources., 1980, Fall.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Human Rights Organizations & Periodicals Directory., 1975.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - National Television Advertisers., 1977-1978.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Publicity binders., 1969-1981.; Boxes 12 and 13
    - Recording industry., 1976, Aug - 1979, Dec.; 2 folders (Box 13, Folders 7 - 8)
    - Television industry/television violence., 1975, Mar - 1980, Jan.; 2 folders (Box 13, Folders 9 - 10)
    - WAVAW., 1976-1980.; 2 folders (Box 13, Folders 11 - 12)
      Articles about WAVAW, press releases, publicity flyers, notes and form letters
  - Work diaries., 1977, 1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 13 and 14
    - Work diary for Julia London., 1977.; 2 folders (Box 13, Folders 13 - 14)
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Amnesty International publications., 1978, Nov.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 38)
      Human rights violations in Ethiopia.
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - Articles by WAVAW., 1976, Apr; 1981, Fall.; 2 folders (Box 14, Folders 39 - 40)
      Organizational Analysis and the Call for Consultation by Tamar Kraut and WAVAW-authored sex education article.
    - Clippings., 1977-1978.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 41)
      Topics include: free enterprise in schools; TV sex; TV violence; violence against women in the media; motherhood; battered women and victimization and unisex writing.
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Female Sexual Mutilations: The Facts and Proposals for Action., 1980, May.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 42)
      Published by Women's International Network News
    - L.A. Commission on Status of Women., 1976, Oct-Dec.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 43)
      Curriculum proposal and class outline for self defense for women proposed by subcommittee on rape and related correspondence
    - LACAAW Survivor Packet., 1982, Nov.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 44)
      Los Angeles Commission on Assaults Against Women's sexual assault Survivor's Packet
    - National Coalition Against Sexual Assault., 1982.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 45)
      10 year anniversary publication titled "Ten Years: 1972-1982 Working Against Sexual Assault."
  - Newsletters., 1974-1993.; Boxes 8, 10, 14 and 21
    - Newsletters (other than WAVAW)., 1976-1982.; 3 folders (Box 14, Folders 46 - 48)
      Newsletters from various women's, feminist, grassroots and women's crisis organizations and related correspondence.
  - Work diaries., 1977, 1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 13 and 14
    - Phone log., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Articles., 1971-1991.; Boxes 1, 2, 4, 7, 8, 10, 14 and 15
    - "The Most Powerful Women in L.A."., 1976, Sept.; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Article by WAVAW., 1977, July.; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 44)
      Music Retailer 1977 article by Julia London and Susan Bechard.
    - Articles about WAVAW., 1978.; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Clippings., 1976-1982.; 2 folders (Box 15, Folders 46 - 47)
      Topics include: Pornography, police-intelligence gathering activities, rednecks and the feminist movement, mental health for sexual minorities and rape
  - Newspapers., 1975-1994.; Oversized boxes 16-18
    - Big Mama Rag (Denver, CO)., 1975, Nov.; 1 issue (v.3-A no.10) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Includes article about "snuff films"
    - Daily Trojan (University of Southern California)., 1982, Mar.; 1 issue (XCI number 46) (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Article about WAVAW
    - EveryWoman/L.A. (Los Angeles Section, National Council of Jewish Women)., 1983, May/June.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Filmex., 1976, Mar-April.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Insert for Los Angeles International Film Exposition March 21-April 4.
    - FREE VENICE BEACHHEAD., 1982, Sept.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Glendale News-Press., 1978, May.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Includes article profiling Julia London and WAVAW.
    - Her-Self., 1976, May.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Editorial by WAVAW re Snuff boycott.
    - Houston Breakthrough., 1976, Aug-Sept.; 1 issue (v.1 no.7) (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Article about WAVAW's "Black and Blue" campaign.
      rehoused in oversized box
    - Impact '79 (Journal of the Institute for Family Research and Education)., 1979, Oct.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Lesbian News., 1983, May; 1994, Aug; 1991, Feb.; 3 issues (v.8 no.10, May 1983; 8/94, August; v.20 no.1, Feb 1991) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Loyolan (Loyola Marymount University)., 1979, Feb.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Majority Report (The Women's Newspaper)., 1977, Apr-Sept.; 3 issues (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Articles about WAVAW's "Black and Blue" campaign, Sadism Masochism and COYOTE.
    - New Women's Times., 1976, Dec.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Articles about Snuff.
    - Ocean Park Perspective (Santa Monica, CA)., 1982, May-June.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Article about WAVAW re Dressed to Kill campaign.
    - Plexus Bay Area Women's Newspaper., 1976, Oct; 1977, Jan.; 2 issues (no.8, no.11) (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Articles about the dissolution of Feminist Economics Network (FEN) and the Conference on Violence Against Women held in San Francisco, Dec. 4th and 5th, 1977.
    - Reader (Los Angeles's Free Weekly)., 1983, May 13.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Sister Advocate., 1978, Aug.; 1 issue (August 25, 1978, Volume IV Number 8) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Sister Courage (Greater Boston's Independent Feminist Newsjournal)., 1976, Apr; 1978, June.; 2 issues (April 1976, Vol.1 No.6; June 1978, Vol.3 No. 4) (Box 16, Folder 18)
      Editorial criticizing boycotting strategies against Snuff and article about WAVAW's WCI boycott.
    - Sister Source (A Midwest Lesbian/Feminist Newspaper)., 1982, June.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The California NOW ACTIVIST., 1983, Winter.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The NOW Times., 1981, Oct, [n.d.].; 2 issues (October 1981, v. IV no.10; n.d.) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Together (The magazine of UCLA women)., 1976, May; 1978, Nov; 1985, May.; 3 issues ( v.3 number 6, May 18, 1976; v.6 number 2 November 1978; May 1986, Special Issue) (Box 16, Folder 22)
      Special issues: Sexism in Education and Women's Survival Guide.
    - University of Washington Daily., 1977, March.; 1 issue (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Diversity The Lesbian Rag., 1991, Feb. (Box 16, Folder 24)
      Separated Material
      1 issue ( v. IV no.1, Feb. 23, 1991)
    - Off Our Backs (A Women's News Journal)., 1971-1994.; 24 issues (v.1 no.2, May 6, 1971; v.2 no. 3, Nov. 1971 - no. 4, Dec. 1971; no. 10, July 1972; v.3 no. 1, Sept. 1972; no. 3, Nov.1972; no. 4, Dec.1972; no. 8, May 1973; no. 10, Sept. 1973; no.12, Nov.1973; v.4, no.2 Dec-Jan 1974; v.8 no. 3, March 1978; no. 4, April 1978; v.9 no. 1, Jan. 1979; no. 9, Oct.1979; v.10 no. 10, Nov.1980; v.22 no. 11, Dec. 1992 (Box 17)
    - BodyPolitic (A Magazine for Gay Liberation)., 1981, Mar.; 1 issue (no. 71, March 1981) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Detroit Women's Press., 1974.; 1 issue (no. 71, March 1981) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - FagRag (Boston, Mass)., 1974, Winter-Spring.; 1 issue (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Fifth Estate (Detroit, MI)., 1974, Feb/Mar.; 1 issue (v.8 no. 22[204], February 16 - March 1, 1974) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Hagborn (A Radical Feminist Newsjournal)., 1981, Spring.; 1 issue (v.2 no. 1, Spring 1981) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Jump Cut (A Review of Contemporary Cinema)., 1981, Mar.; 1 issue (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Special Section: Lesbians and Film
    - LA Star (An Unauthorized Newspaper)., 1976, July.; 1 issue (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Lavender Woman (Chicago, IL)., 1974, May.; 1 issue (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Lesbian Contradiction (A Journal of Irreverent Feminism)., 1983, Fall.; 1 issue (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - The Radical Therapist/Rough Times (Somerville, MA)., 1972-1975.; 7 issues (July 1972, Sept 1972, April-May 1973, June-July 1973, Sept-Oct 1973, March-April-May 1974, Spring 1975) (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - MATRIX - Women's Free Monthly Newsmagazine., March 1983. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - Story of O., 1965.; 1 book (Box 20, Folder 13)
      by Pauline Reage
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Mother Jones., 1976, 1981.; 3 issues (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Ms.., 1990, Sept; 1992, Jan/Feb; 1992, July/Aug; 1993, Mar/Apr.; 4 issues (Box 21, Folders 2 - 3)
  - Newsletters., 1974-1993.; Boxes 8, 10, 14 and 21
    - Newsletters (other than WAVAW)., 1974, 1991, 1993.; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Includes partial run of Lesbian Newsletter New Zealand (1993-1994) and newsletters related to women's health services
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Swedish Women's Magazine "Q"., 1982, Jan.; 1 issue (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - The New Republic., 1966, Nov.; 1 issue (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit Brief., 1984.; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Brief on pornography
  - Periodicals., 1966-1993.; Boxes 5, 10, 11, 21, 22, 23 and 24
    - Amazon Milwaukee's Feminist Press., 1980, Aug/Sept.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Breakthrough (San Francisco, CA)., 1985, May.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Christopher Street (New York, NY)., 1977-1978.; 4 issues (Box 22, Folder 3)
      1977, Feb; 1978, Mar; 1979, Feb; 1979, Mar
    - Commonground Magazine (Glendale, CA)., 1983, Apr.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Communities Journal of Cooperation (Stelle, IL)., 1984/5, Winter.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Country Women (San Francisco, CA)., 1973, June-Oct.; 2 issues (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Dyke Review (San Francisco, CA)., 1992, Summer.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - FUSE (Toronto, Ontario, CA)., 1991, Fall.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Graffiti (New York, NY)., 1968.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Heresies (New York, NY)., 1978, 1980.; 2 issues (Box 22, Folder 10)
      Issue #6 On Women and Violence and Issue #10 Women and Music
    - Issues in Radical Therapy (Springfield, IL)., 1987.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Journal of Communication., 1981, Spring; 1981, Autumn.; 2 issues (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Law for the People (New York, NY)., 1979-1980.; 1 issue (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Journal of Communication., 1980, Spring, 1980 Autumn.; 2 issues (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Lesbian Tide (Los Angeles, CA)., 1980, May/June.; 1 issue (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Liberation (New York, NY)., 1972-1973.; 2 issues (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Moving Out (Detroit, MI)., 1973-1974.; 2 issues (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - National Lampoon (New York, NY)., 1971, July.; 1 issue (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - No More Cages Women's Prison Newsletter (Brooklyn, NY)., [1984].; 1 issue (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Notes From the Second Year: Radical Feminism (New York, NY)., 1970.; 1 issue (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - NYQ (New York, NY)., 1992, Apr.; 1 issue (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - OUT/LOOK National Lesbian & Gay Quarterly (San Francisco, CA)., 1988-1992.; 7 issues (Box 23, Folders 8 - 11)
    - OutWeek (New York, NY)., 1990, Aug, Dec.; 2 issues (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Quest a feminist quarterly., 1977, Spring.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Race, class & culture
    - Radical America., 1979, Sept-Oct.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ramparts (Berkeley, CA)., 1971, Sept.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Scanlan's Monthly., 1970, Mar.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Spare Rib (London)., 1981, June.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - State and Mind (Boston, MA)., 1977.; 2 issues (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - The Tide (Los Angeles, CA)., 1974, Apr.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Trouble & Strife (Norwich, Britain)., 1991, Spring.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Up from Under (New York, NY)., 1970, May/June.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Visibilities (New York, NY)., 1988, Sept/Oct.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Woman of Power (Cambridge, MA)., 1990, Summer.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Women & Film (Santa Monica, CA)., 1972.; 1 issue (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Women A Journal of Liberation (Baltimore, MD)., 1970-1972.; 3 issues (Box 24, Folder 14)
      1970, Spring; 1972, vol. 3 no. 1-2
    - WorkForce (Canyon, CA)., 1972-1974.; 3 issues (Box 24)
      1972, July-Aug: Vocations for Social Change; 1973, May-June: Research and 1974, Nov: Resource Guide
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Annual reports., 1977-1979.; 5 folders (Box 25, Folder 1 - 5)
      Arthur Andersen & Co., and Warner Communications Inc.
  - Directories., 1974-1990.; Boxes 1, 4, 13 and 25
    - Catalogs., 1974-1978.; 4 folders (Box 25, Folders 6 - 9)
      Film-Makers' Cooperative Catalogue No. 6, Mecanorma Graphic Products, New College of California School of Law and Tactype.
  - Books., 1965-1990.; Boxes 1, 10, 11, 20 and 25
    - Civil Rights Issues of Euro-Ethnic Americans in the United States: Opportunities and Challenges., 1979, Dec.; 1 book (Box 25)
      A Consultation Sponsored by the United States Commission on Civil Rights, Chicago, Illinois
    - Clive Inside the Record Business., 1975.; 1 book (Box 25)
      by Clive Davis with James Willwerth
    - Free Fire Zone Short Stories by Vietnam Veterans., 1973.; 1 book (Box 25)
      edited by Wayne Karlin; Basil T. Paquet and Larry Rottmann
  - Reports., 1970-1984.; Boxes 1, 3, 10, 11, 14, 25, 26 and 27
    - Booklets., 1976, [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Topics include: citizen committees, public service advertising and press coverage.
    - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights publications., 1977-1981.; 8 folders (Box 26, Folders 2 - 9)
      Topics include: women and minorities in television, civil rights, Title IX, affirmative action, fair housing, immigration, and disabled people.
    - Conferences., 1977-1981.; 3 folders (Box 27, Folders 1 - 3)
      Conference on Women & the Law, WAVPM proposed conference "Feminist Perspectives on Pornography," and "Women Helping Women the Path to Leadership."
    - Consumerism at the Crossroads., 1977.; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Commissioned by Sentry Insurance